Go

Go

Go

Privacy Policy
==============

Adopted: November 1, 2006 PRIVACY POLICY

We are strongly committed to protecting the privacy of your personal information. The policies below are applicable to the bellevuearts.org website (“Website”) produced and maintained by Bellevue Arts Museum. (collectively “Bellevue Arts Museum” or “we”, “us”, or “our”). We have established this security and privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) to let you know the kinds of personal information we may gather during your visit to the Website, why we gather your information, what we use your personal information for, when we might disclose your personal information, and how you can manage your personal information.

Please be advised that the practices described in this Privacy Policy apply only to information gathered through this Website and do not necessarily reflect our practices with respect to information gathered off- line.

**By visiting our Website, you are accepting the practices described in our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Website and exit immediately. We reserve the right to modify or amend the terms of our Privacy Policy from time to time without notice. Your continued use of our Website and our affiliate sites following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or do not see your concerns addressed here, you should contact us by email at [\[email protected\]](https://www.bellevuearts.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

#### **What Information About Me Is Collected And Stored?**

Bellevue Arts Museum adheres to the highest standards of ethical practices in all of our operations and is dedicated to protecting the privacy of all visitors to our Website. Our privacy policy is simple: Except as disclosed below, we do not sell, barter, give away, or rent your personal information to any company outside of Bellevue Arts Museum. In addition, one of the basic principles we have followed in designing this Website is that we ask for only the information we need to provide the service you have requested. As a result, what information we collect and store depends almost entirely on how you choose to make use of our Website and our services.

**Personal Information**

We collect and store information that you enter into this Website. For example, when you join the museum, make a donation or purchase online tickets, we collect and store some or all of the following information that you provide: name, billing address, email address, telephone number, credit card number and expiration date. This information is used to provide the products and services that you have ordered or requested, to process orders, to send order and donation confirmations and to provide customer service. Registration may also be required and Personal Information may also be collected in certain portions of the Website in which you specifically and knowingly provide such information, e.g. community postings (i.e., chat or bulletin boards), suggestions, or customer service requests. Some of this information also may be used to contact you about sales, special offers, and new site features, unless you have opted not to receive promotional communications in connection with this Website.

**Anonymous Information; Traffic Data**

Through your use of the Website, we may also gather certain information that does not identify you individually (“Anonymous Information”). Generally, this information is collected through "traffic data" and may involve the use of "Cookies," "IP addresses" or other numeric codes used to identify a computer. We collect and store certain other information automatically whenever you interact with this Website. For example, we collect your IP address, browser information and reference site domain name every time you visit this Website. We also collect information regarding user traffic patterns and site usage. This information is used to analyze and improve this Website and to provide our users with a fulfilling experience.

**Use of Cookies and Spyware**

Like many websites, we use “cookies”, which are files stored on your computer’s hard drive by your browser. Cookies help us to identify members and to optimize their experience. We need browser cookies to be enabled for certain areas of the Website. For example, we use cookies in educational interactions (e.g. to track your progress in the game) and gallery slide shows (e.g. to track your progress in the slide show). "Cookies" in and of themselves do not personally identify users, although they do identify a user's computer. Our website never uses “Cookies” to retrieve information from your computer that was not originally sent in a “Cookie.” Most browsers accept cookies automatically but allow you to disable them. We recommend that you leave cookies “turned on” so that we can offer you a better experience on this Website. You may occasionally get “Cookies” from our advertisers. We do not control these “Cookies,” and these “Cookies” are not subject to our “Cookie” policy.

We never use or install spyware on your computer, nor do we use spyware to retrieve information from your computer.

**Newsletters**

We collect e-mail addresses and zip codes of all users who subscribe to our weekly newsletter and RSS feeds. This information is not shared with any third parties for any purposes. Anyone who wishes to stop receiving this newsletter can, at any time, click on the “Unsubscribe” feature located within each newsletter.

**Email Communication**

We provide free monthly enews and evites to keep you up-to-date on Bellevue Arts Museum programs and events. We do not sell, rent or share your email information with anyone. You can subscribe and unsubscribe to receive this information at any time.

**Surveys**

We deploy surveys online and on location (in order to get information) to help us understand our audience. You may decide whether or not you want to answer our survey questions. No personal information from these surveys is disclosed to third party organizations. We do compile the (survey question) results and may publish them or share them with other parties.

#### Is Information Collected From Children?

In any section of the website that requests personal information, children 12 years of age and under are reminded to obtain permission from a parent or guardian before supplying the requested information.

#### How We Use Your Information?

Our email and mailing lists are used primarily to send notices about our museum activities. Except as disclosed in this Security and Privacy Policy, we do not sell, rent or share our contact information with commercial businesses. Occasionally, we trade our membership lists with sister arts organizations. We may also use this list for our annual contribution drive. If we propose to permit any use of your Personal Information, you may instruct us not to allow such contact.

**Customer Service and Feedback**

We may use your Personal Information to fulfill orders, provide customer service, track your compliance with the Website’s rules and regulations, or for editorial and feedback purposes (to the extent that is explained when you provide the information). In the event we plan to publicly post any of your Personal Information on a Website (as, for instance, a letter), you are provided prior notification of such posting and given the option of preventing such posting.

**Use of Anonymous Information**

We use Anonymous Information to help us determine how people use parts of the Website and who our readers are so we can improve our Website and ensure that it is as appealing as we can make it for as many people as possible. We also use Anonymous Information to provide statistical "ratings" information in aggregated form to our partners and other third parties about how our users collectively use the website. We may also use or share Anonymous Information (or other information, other than Personal Information) in any other manner that we deem appropriate or necessary.

**Third-party Agents**

We occasionally have third party agents, subsidiaries, affiliates and partners that perform functions on our behalf, such as marketing, analytics, credit card processing, providing customer service, fraud protection, etc. These entities have access to the Personal Information needed to perform their functions and are contractually obligated to maintain the confidentiality and security of that Personal Information. They are restricted from using, selling, distributing or altering this data in any way other than to provide the requested services to the Website.

**Emergency Situations**

We may also use or disclose Personal Information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (a) conform to applicable law or comply with legal process served on us or the Website; (b) protect and defend our rights or property, the Website or our users, and (c) act under emergency circumstances to protect the personal safety of the museum, our affiliates, agents, or the users of the Website or the public.

#### What Steps Are Taken To Keep Personal Information Secure?

The security of all Personal Information associated with you is of utmost concern to us. We exercise great care in providing secure transmission of your information from your PC to our servers. Personal Information collected by our websites is stored in secure operating environments that are not available to the public. In many instances, such as in the case of credit card numbers and all on-line purchases, the Personal Information is encrypted before you conduct your transaction. Only those employees who need access to your Personal Information in order to do their jobs are allowed access, each having signed confidentiality agreements. Any employee who violates our privacy and/or security policies is subject to disciplinary action, including possible termination and civil and/or criminal prosecution.

To protect the security of your information during transmission, we use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. Most browsers will give a visual indication of when your connection is secure. For example, Internet Explorer will show a lock icon in the lower right of the browser window. If you obtain a membership, buy tickets, or make a donation through this Website, you will be asked to set up an account and provide an email address and password. You must provide an appropriate email address and password in order to access account information. In order to help protect your personal information further, you should be careful about providing your password to others. If you wish to cancel your password, or if you become aware of any loss, theft or unauthorized use of your password, please contact the museum by email at [\[email protected\]](https://www.bellevuearts.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

While we make reasonable efforts to safeguard your Personal Information once we receive it, no transmission of data over the Internet or any other public network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or information we transmit to you from our Website, and you do so at your own risk.

#### What Happens When I Link To or From Another Website?

This Website may contain links to other websites operated by affiliates of Bellevue Arts Museum or third parties. Please be advised that the practices described in this Privacy Policy do not apply to information gathered through these other websites. These other sites may also send their own cookies to you, collect your data or solicit your personal information. Always be aware of where you end up. We are not responsible for the actions and privacy policies of third parties and other websites. We encourage you to be aware of when you leave this Website and to read the privacy policies of each and every website that you visit.

#### Public Areas, Chat Rooms and Newsgroups

Please remember that any information you share in public areas, such as message boards or feedback sections, becomes public, and therefore this Privacy Policy does not apply to any information you choose to make public. Please be careful about what you disclose and do not post any Personal Information that you expect to keep private.

#### Governing Law/Assignment

Our Website is published in the United States and is intended for users from the United States. U. S. law shall govern in any and all disputes, including privacy or defamation issues or otherwise. We may change its ownership or corporate organization while providing the website and services. As a result, please be aware that we may transfer your information to another company that is affiliated with us or with which we have merged. Under such circumstances Bellevue Arts Museum would to the extent possible require the acquiring party to follow the practices described in this Privacy Policy, as it may be amended from time to time.

#### Changes to This Policy

We are committed to maintaining our position as a premier Website on the Internet. As our Website continues to develop, we may add new services and features to our Website. In the event that these additions affect our Privacy Policy, this document will be updated appropriately. We will post those changes prominently so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and whether we will disclose it to anyone. We do, however, recommend that you read this Privacy Policy each time you use our website in case you missed our notice of changes to the Privacy Policy.

#### Opt-Out and Correction Procedures

You always may opt-out of receiving future e-mail messages and newsletters. We provide you with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request information about you. There are several ways in which you can tell us whether or not you want to receive promotional communications from us. You will have an opportunity to change selections by clicking on an “unsubscribe” hyperlink contained in promotional emails we send to you. We also permit you to correct or update Personal Information that you have previously provided to us.

#### Who do I talk to if I have more questions?

Questions regarding this statement should be emailed to [\[email protected\]](https://www.bellevuearts.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). To return to the Website, please use the "Back" button on your browser. 

### Sign up for the  
latest from BAM.

        Gallery & Store Hours:  
        Mondays & Tuesdays: Closed  
        Wednesdays – Sundays: 11am – 5pm  
        Artful Evening (07/15): Closed
    
        510 Bellevue Way NE  
        Bellevue, WA 98004

[Privacy Policy](https://www.bellevuearts.org/privacy-policy) | [Contact Us](https://www.bellevuearts.org/about-us/contact-us) | [Jobs & Internships](https://www.bellevuearts.org/about-us/our-community/jobs-internships) | © 2020 Bellevue Arts Museum. All Rights Reserved.

x
